export const verbPracticeDataItaliano = {
  2: [
    { prompt: "Io", answer: "sono" },
    { prompt: "Tu", answer: "sei" },
    { prompt: "Lui", answer: "è" },
    { prompt: "Lei", answer: "è" },
    { prompt: "sono", answer: "io" },
    { prompt: "sei", answer: "tu" },
    { prompt: "è", answer: "lui/lei" }
  ],
  3: [
    { prompt: "Io", answer: "ho" },
    { prompt: "Tu", answer: "hai" },
    { prompt: "Lui", answer: "ha" },
    { prompt: "Lei", answer: "ha" },
    { prompt: "ho", answer: "io" },
    { prompt: "hai", answer: "tu" },
    { prompt: "ha", answer: "lui/lei" }
  ]
};
